— CYNTHIA MOJICA —

Sacramento, CA · (916) 289-4097 · cmojica1231@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/cynthia-mojica

CERTIFICATION

- LICENSED REAL ESTATE
 SALESPERSON
- RCFE ADMINISTRATOR
- VANGUARD ADMINISTRATOR

PROFILE

RACF Administrator at State Controller's Office. Her role is to provide technical installation, configuration, administration, performance... access and profile issue subject matter expert. Administration and management of complex RACF infrastructure with multiple databases.

My background in mainframe and troubleshooting gave me desire to seek a more challenging job. I continue to grow my skillsets in the areas of front and backend of programming.

EDUCATION

BS OF BUSINESS MANAGEMENT

CAVSU - PHILIPPINES

CODING BOOTCAMP

6 MONTHS - UC DAVIS

SKILLS & INTEREST

- IBM RACF SECURITY SYSTEM
- COBOL, CICS, DYL280
- IBM UTILITIES,
 TSO/ISPF/MVS/JCL/panels
- VANGUARD
- TRAINING IN WEB
 DEVELOPMENT
- TRAVEL

EXPERIENCE

Student Full Stack Flex Web Development – UC DAVIS

June 2020 – Dec 2020

Designing and developing various web applications using technologies that include JavaScript, CSS, Node.js, Bootstrap, Firebase, MySQL, and React • Collaborate with other developers on group projects workflow using GitHub

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SPECIALIST I

June 2012- present

Mainframe Access Control – Perform and provide complex detailed Resource Access Control Facility (RACF) administration services for an IBM mainframe MVS z/OZ, JES3 system, and secure file exchange systems using Vanguard, and administration tools and applications such as CICS, IDMS, ISPF, TSO, MultiSess and JCL services.

STAFF PROGRAMMER ANALYST

April 2007 – June 2012

Provide technical support to Production Operations (PO) and programmer in creating and altering Dialogs and Job Control Language (JCL). Assist with production processing, modify schedules and support Staff in system testing. Created panels and manipulating skeleton through JCL program. Install new Mark IV processes into production and programs. Provide on-line monitor support for customers. Develop and provide operations training on specialized topic or new PO applications such as utility programs, the conversion processes, FTP, ESP and JCL.